A P Hello friends, welcome everyone to this
channel, I am yours, friends, I am 127
staff member and friends, it is about to be 10 o'clock,
friends, we are going to talk about the
merger of ICICI Lombard and Bhartiya Ekta
or about the Bharti that ICICI is going to
acquire, but
before starting the video, friends, if
you are new to our channel, you have
not yet subscribed to our channel, then
definitely subscribe to our channel,
friends, and along with that small
bell icon on the side,
you must definitely
click on that notification because if it is clicked, then as soon as
we upload a video,
you will get a notification
and you will get the total information
and friends, secondly, if you
want to join our channel, for this
I have kept it in the description,
you can join us by going there
and now let's move ahead and talk
about ICICI Lombard General Insurance, it is a great company,
friends, ICICI Bank is an oil bank.  It is also
known by a good name, has a very good
performance, along with this the insurance company is also having a
big problem, if you see then it is
sharing almost lifetime high flame, from
here it is a very big level, very
rarely a company gets to
see ICICI, friends and an
attempt is being made to settle above by breaking it, if
you talk about Bharti AXA, it is a
good company, there is a merger of two companies and if you will have
fun then it will be a joint venture inverter, it is a
joint venture of two companies
and today both the companies have taken a decision together that
they have to unite their insurance business or
final you with this, so a
tweet has been done, there is detail that in this way this
matter will move forward, how will this matter move forward, what will the
shareholders get,
what will be the buying and selling range, there are many things, so let's move forward
step by step,
but the use was that ICICI Lombard General
Insurance is a subsidiary of Bharti Enterprises,
forget that once it
falls, all its promoted businesses, 38
general insurances, will be ruined.  By
buying all the stocks of Bharti Enterprises, it is going to make it equal.
Due to this, there was a lot of rise in the stock this morning.
Quick bread and it closed at minus one percent.
Bharti
Enterprises is an effective one percent
stake holder in Bharti AXA General
Insurance and this is a French company, it is a
349 person company.
If you go and see, the French Aishwarya
Prince's extra company is
in the insurance business. Bharti
Enterprises is not in the financial business,
but this joint venture was done here.
If you pay attention further, Bharti
Enterprises has been trying to consolidate the finance business since around 2016 and even
before that.
Due to this,
they had also talked to Reliance.
In 2016, they used to have about 7.4 percent stake,
then they had a vow to sell it. Now this matter has
not progressed further, nothing has happened,
so you should go and the matter has come up again after four years
and this time it is
ICICI Lombard.
If you see the interest shown in this, then Indian
General Insurance had
increased
its business by 38% around March, the premium it
collects is around 3157 crores
and if we compare it with the last
18-19, then it used to be 2250
which has increased to 3157, so there is a
great improvement in the business as well
and if this business alarm free ICICI
tracks it further then here
they will get a lot of road network, a
lot of new lines to
which they can send their cross-vault portfolio
and at the same time the
network
is very important friends, it will come to them, the
information will come to them, so this is
a very good initiative for ICICI
and because of this I don't know I am
not able to understand why the rise in the share which should have happened
today did not happen and a slight
decline was seen and perhaps the share in me too will
reach a lifetime high.
Therefore, people here are
expecting a correction. If there is a correction, it
happens. Friends, here you will definitely be
advised to buy
after the correction. In fact, this news will be
seen. Many of them are
waiting for the stock to fall and as
many people book profits, those who
think in advance and who think ahead will
pick it up in the fallen stock. Now let's take the matter forward.
Vikram Bharti AXA, which is the
channel partner of the policy holder, their
chief number
person here is Bhargav Dasgupta. He says
that if Bharti adds another one and converts the
Indian education business into tissue paper, then the
system of doing business here, which is slow, will remain seamless, there will be
continuity and there will be no decline in their service
standards.
Everything will
continue exactly as it is going on, only the
name of ICICI will
come up somewhere, so there has been no service related issue.
And now talking about the buy,
look here, there is a reservation for a cupboard.  We have
accepted that there will be
no monetary transaction here, but only
share transactions. So, the thing is that from the
side of Bharti AXA, they will
get two shares of ICICI Lombard. If
they fold 115 shares of Bharti AXA
through Bharti AXA, in exchange for 115 shares of Bharti AXA,
you will get only two shares of ICICI.
This has got the approval of the vote and
both Bharti AXA and Ekta have given their approval
and this matter is moving forward.
Now after the approval of the board,
there comes the matter of approval of the
Insurance Regulatory and Development
Authority of IRDA, Competition Commission of India Stock
Exchange. With this, the approval of all these shareholders and their
creditors as well as these CLP
people is also necessary here. Once this
approval is received, then this deal will
come into processing and the share
exchange will start.
Here, somewhere I feel
that there is a slight slowdown in thinking on Bharti AXA.
Because there
is a flaw in exchange for 115 shares, even if
it seems right in valuation, then it can be a
little ahead or behind somewhere, those who do
not understand the concept of lock valuation will find
this thing a little bit wrong,
but see, it does not happen like this,
zero has to be seen as per the valuation and
you will have to learn to calculate the valuation
of your company because if this thing happens then the
other company is giving you less shares,
this thinking is a little wrong, so you will
definitely learn it so that you can actually understand the company from which you bought your bike, so
this was my details friends,
if you liked the video about ICICI Lombard and Bharatiya Ekta, then
definitely subscribe to the channel or
instead of liking, share the video with your friends
and join the Telegram channel,
very soon in the next video, till then
thank you very much for